# **Danny Di Iorio**

302 − 1550 W 10th Ave. ↑ Vancouver, BC

250-701-8604

dannydiiorio@gmail.com 💌

www.linkedin.com/in/danielrdiiorio in

www.github.com/ddiiorio #

### **Profile**

My strong motivation, excellent communication skills, and professional attitude would be a great addition to your organization. I have years of positive relationships with business and individual clients. Through these relationships, I have gained experience with answering multi-line telephones, greeting, and assisting clients of all ages and backgrounds.

### **Technical Skills**

- Languages: Java, JavaScript, learning C
- Web Design: Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Ionic
- Database Design: SQL, Microsoft SQL Server, Microsoft Visio
- Tools: GitHub, Photoshop, Eclipse, Microsoft Office, WebStorm, Google SketchUp

# **Academic Project Experience**

### Relational Database Design & SQL Projects / BCIT

**MAY - JULY 2017** 

- Designed a relational database system for managing data regarding a university alumni association
- Used Microsoft SQL Server Management to create a new database and execute SQL statements to insert, update, delete and view data, and create and execute stored procedures and triggers
- Links to view projects here: https://ddiiorio.github.io/BCIT/database.html

## Mealio Web App / BCIT Project Term – Metro Vancouver

APRIL - MAY 2017

- LINK: www.mealio.tk
- Developed a web app in teams of 5 using ReactJS, Bootstrap, Google Firebase, HTML, CSS
- Agile scrum framework was used to manage the development process, including 3 one-week sprints to accomplish specific goals
- Utilized a Gitflow Workflow to develop individual features on local branches, then merging to develop for testing/review, and finally to master for official releases

# Personal Project Experience

## Concert Schedule Web/Android App / Ionic Framework

AUGUST - SEPT 2017

- Developed a minimalist app to keep track of past and upcoming concert dates, sorted chronologically
- Work in progress
- Work in progress

### **Bullfrog Spas Web Work / South Island Fireplace & Spas**

JUNE - AUGUST 2017

- LINK: www.southislandfireplace.com/bullfrog\_spas.html
- Created new page on past employer's website for their new spa product line
- Developed in the Bootstrap framework for sleek and responsive UI, nested HTML elements within the Bootstrap grid, styled with CSS

# **Danny Di Iorio**

# **Other Work Experience**

### Design & Sales Consultant / Elements Outdoor Inc.

SEPT 2007 - PRESENT

- Render 3D models of outdoor kitchens for sales and production purposes using Google SketchUp
- B2B and customer-direct sales throughout Canada
- Generate accurate and detailed sales/marketing documents, reports, and quotes

### **Shipper / MP Lighting, Vancouver**

JUNE 2017 - AUGUST 2017

- Arrange all shipments by preparing bills of lading, customs forms, invoices, and other documents
- Coordinate with other departments to plan, organize, and schedule all shipments to prevent delays

### Inventory Manager / South Island Fireplace & Spas, Duncan

SEPT 2010 - DEC 2016

- Create and maintain accurate records of incoming shipments and invoices
- Interact/negotiate with numerous suppliers on a daily basis
- Design and maintain the company website/emails/domain (www.southislandfireplace.com)
- IT support for all computers/printers/phones on company network

# **Education & Training**

### Computer Systems Technology / BCIT, Burnaby

JAN 2017 - PRESENT

90% GPA in Winter & Spring/Summer terms

**Business Administration Diploma / Vancouver Island University** 

MAY 2007

Red Cross Occupational First-Aid Level 1 / Red Cross, Victoria

**MARCH 2016** 

#### **Interests & Activities**

- Import cars working on and modifying my cars, meeting and sharing experiences with other auto enthusiasts
- Sports playing hockey has been a part of my life since a child